(Sheldon:)Are you using trains to trick me
into giving you advice?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)All right, then.
(Sheldon:)You should take a third train
(Sheldon:)where you audition
for the movie
(Sheldon:)but hold off
on making a career decision
(Sheldon:)until you have more information.
(Penny:)Oh. You're right.
(Penny:)I'm worried about something
that hasn't even happened yet.
(Raj:)Huh.
(Penny:)You are a wise man.
Well, Penny, who's smarter:
the wise man
(Sheldon:)or the person who comes to him
for advice?
(Penny:)Oh, I guess you're right.
(Penny:)Maybe it is the person who asks.
(Sheldon:)No, it's the wise man.
(Sheldon:)That's why he's called
the wise man.
(Sheldon:)You know how I know that?
(Sheldon:)I'm the wise man.
(Penny:)I'm sorry. What was I thinking?
(Sheldon:)Uh, just out
of curiosity,
(Sheldon:)why didn't you ask Leonard
for advice about this?
(groans)